'use strict';

const QUESTIONS = [
  {
    question: 'What did Toyota produce before maufacturing automobiles?',
    answers: ['Paper', 'Tools', 'Sewing Machines', 'Weapons' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Sewing Machines'
  },
  {
    question: 'What year did Toyota manufacture it’s first passenger vehicle?',
    answers: ['1911', '1935', '1986', '1945' ],
    correctAnswer: '1935'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the model name of the first passenger vehicle Toyota produced?',
    answers: ['Corolla', 'Ichi', 'Prius', 'Model A1' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Model A1'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the model name of the first truck Toyota ever produced?',
    answers: ['Model A2', 'Model G1', 'Model T', 'Tacoma' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Model G1'
  },
  {
    question: 'What model Toyota automobile is the best-selling nameplate in the world?',
    answers: ['Prius', 'Echo', 'Corolla', 'Camry' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Corolla'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many Corollas have been produced?',
    answers: ['more than 40 million', 'more than 100 million', 'more than 200 million', 'more than 500 million' ],
    correctAnswer: 'more than 40 million'
  },
  {
    question: 'The Passionate Pursuit of Potential” is the slogan for what division of Toyota?',
    answers: ['Acura', 'Infiniti', 'TRD', 'Lexus' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Lexus'
  },
  {
    question: 'What year was the Lexus division created?',
    answers: ['1940', '1970', '1983', '1990' ],
    correctAnswer: '1983'
  },
  {
    question: 'Toyota is the largest company in Japan.  How does it rank against the world’s other largest automotive manufacturers?',
    answers: ['First largest manufacturer', 'Second largest manufacturer', 'Third largest manufacturer', 'Four largest manufacturer' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Second largest manufacturer'
  },
  {
    question: 'On average, how many vehicles does Toyota produce per year?',
    answers: ['1,000,000', '2,000,000', '3,000,000', 'more than 5,000,000' ],
    correctAnswer: 'more than 5,000,000'
  },
  {
    question: 'What year did Toyota start participating in Formula-1?',
    answers: ['1977', '1982', '1996', '2002' ],
    correctAnswer: '2002'
  },
  {
    question: 'What brands are currently owned by Toyota?',
    answers: ['Citroen, Peugeot, Mazda', 'Honda, Acura, Mugen', 'Nismo, Nissan, Infiniti', 'Lexus, Scion, Daihatsu, Hino Motors, Subaru, Isuzu' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Lexus, Scion, Daihatsu, Hino Motors, Subaru, Isuzu'
  },
  {
    question: 'What year did Toyota produce it’s 100-millionth vehicle?',
    answers: ['1990', '1999', '2004', '2015' ],
    correctAnswer: '2004'
  },
  {
    question: 'In 1951, the Japanese car manufacturer launched a series of four-wheel-drive vehicles which became Toyota’s longest running series. What its the name of this series?',
    answers: ['Tacoma', '4Runner', 'Land Cruiser', 'Highlander' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Land Cruiser'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the biggest SUV built by Toyota?',
    answers: ['Land Cruiser', 'Mega Cruiser', '4Runner', 'Sequoia' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Mega Cruiser'
  },
  {
    question: 'In 2012, what vehicle was used to tow the Atlantis Space Shuttle to it’s final destination?',
    answers: ['Toyota Tundra', 'Toyota Tacoma', 'Toyota 4Runner', 'Toyota Mega Cruiser' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Toyota Tundra'
  },
  {
    question: 'In 1970, Toyota released their first mass-produced sports car. This model sports car participated in the World Rally Championship and won many times. What is the name of this particular model?',
    answers: ['Toyota Celica', 'Toyota Supra', 'Toyota MR2', 'Toyota Corolla' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Toyota Celica'
  },
  {
    question: 'Toyota ended production of the Celica after producing it’s seventh generation.  What year did Toyota end the production of the Celica?',
    answers: ['2000', '2006', '2010', '2012' ],
    correctAnswer: '2006'
  },
  {
    question: 'What Toyota produced Hybrid-vehicle holds the record for being the best-selling hybrid car in the world?',
    answers: ['Toyota Rav4', 'Toyota Corolla', 'Toyota Echo', 'Toyota Prius' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Toyota Prius'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many Priuses have been sold?',
    answers: ['3 million', 'Over 4 million', '10 million', '100 million' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Over 4 million'
  }

];